One issue identified in this chapter is that delays in the vendor procurement process have
یکی از موضوعاتی که در این فصل مشخص شده است این است که تأخیر در روند خرید فروشنده است
delayed the project finished date past the grant expiration date. This is a top priority
تأخیر در پروژه به پایان رسیده تاریخ گذشته کمک هزینه ای برای تاریخ انقضاء هست؛این یک اولویت اصلی است
issue because the grant money covers most of the expenses for the hospital scheduling
موضوع را به دلیل اینکه هزینه کمکی بیشتری برای هزینه های سیستم برنامه ریزی بیمارستانیرا پوشش می دهد
system. One solution to this problem shows promise. Your sponsor and the Change Review
یک راه حل برای این مشکل نویدی است که اسپانسر یا حامی شما و بررسی در تغییرات می دهد
Board have approved the change request for the vendor to perform the work for this solution.
هیئت مدیره تقاضای تغییر برای فروشنده را در انجام این کار برای این راه حل تصویب کرده است
The change request is available in the exercise files. You have created a schedule, budget,
تقاضای تغییر در پرونده های تمرین موجود است . شما یک برنامه ، بودجه را خلق کرده اید
resource plan, risk plan, communication plan and quality plan for the project in this challenge,
برنامه منابع ، برنامه ریسک ، برنامه ارتباطات و برنامه کیفیت برای پروژه در این چالش هست
determine which of these tools and plans need to be updated for this change request. Provide
تعیین کنید که برای این درخواست تغییر ، کدام یک از این ابزارها و برنامه ها به روز شوند
an overview of the changes that need to be made. Take about 20 minutes for this challenge.
ارائه مروری بر تغییراتی که باید انجام شود برای این چالش حدود 20 دقیقه وقت بگذارید
After you complete the challenge, you can head to the exercise files to take a look
بعد از اتمام این چالش ، می توانید به پرونده های تمرین بروید تا نگاهی بیندازید
at my solution.
در راه حل من